{
    "id": "1c6196dfeb424fa9b4e273fbf04db4dc",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. somewhat pompous, he was an entertaining companion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01464d33d53b40b18bd78357d6e1c6d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………….. a knave nor a fool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8de5f1ebcf0b4de59664a2d0ade1e2e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sells mangoes ………………….. oranges.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1fc1c8ec4ff240a3b604b6b87b30c5a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. there is life, there is hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a367b0083de9487a85d69f88adedc0b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me ………………….. he would leave tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96b4673272a94ef9b5cb0363b94a6564"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. cannot be cured must be endured.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7221add9a46042cd8d26cd2d6dcad81c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We love him ………………… he is faithful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7027302b347f471b8d4f1c69ac038136"
        },
        {
            "question": "We decided to set out ………………… it was late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f9a82a9920944ca7827c95f5e31d3d0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sheep ……………….. the oxen are grazing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d581861173f47cc8e6551343557fa66"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………… she looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "02f9dc57ec8541398cdeeb1907c82d76"
        }
    ]
}